(Yuri) Mr. Igawa! (Igawa) Which one are you?
(Tsumura) Strange things are always happening.
It's not just Masaki Igawa, there's something about that city itself...
Huh! (Kousaka) Masaki Igawa
Is it really that important to look like Yusuke Ninomiya?
(Tsujimoto) That person killed someone.
should not be tolerated for any reason
Are you friends?
Again... Memories I don't know are floating in my head
Are you okay? Masaki Igawa and Yusuke Ninomiya
It's the same person
♬〜
≪Someone said≫
≪You can't change the past≫
♬〜
≪But...≫
≪The meaning of the past can be changed≫
≪But that's a beautiful thing≫
≪How nice it would be if I could change the past≫
≪How nice it would be if I could forget the past≫
《I'm sorry it happened like this》
(Kousaka)《Are you used to that life yet? 》
(Kousaka)《You haven't lived a regular life for over 10 years, right?》
《Yes, but it's strange》
``Even though I killed someone, I still get three meals.''
I feel better than when I was there.
``Are you two okay? 》
(Kousaka)《It looks like she will get married and have children》
《I see. Good.》
♬〜
≪I thought I was going to forget everything≫
《What? 》
(Kousaka)《He was hit by a truck and died instantly...》
《Like that...》
≪Two years ago, I was told that Yusuke Ninomiya had died≫
≪But just before being released from prison...≫
≪Informant reporter
I found a man who is just like Ninomiya≫
♬〜
《He was a model prisoner since Musashino Prison opened》
《Sorry for the inconvenience》
(Kousaka) 《Is there somewhere you want to go? 》
《What you want to eat》
《Have you ever heard the name Masaki Igawa? 》
《Igawa? 》 《While inside
A reporter I know also told me about Ninomiya and his friends.
I asked him to look at it.》
《The reporter recently
I found someone who looks just like Ninomiya》
《Is that Igawa? " "yes"
《Isn't it similar to someone else? 》
《Your friend passed away two years ago》
《Better forget about it》
(Kousaka)《You have suffered enough》
《A day trip hot spring was opened along the Akigawa River》
《Around there》
≪There was no way I could forget≫
(Mitsuru/Takako)《Hello》 (Mayumi)《Hello》
《Ah Ma-kun, welcome back》 《Are you shopping now? 》
《Yes, food will be ready soon》 《I'll have it》
"thank you"
(Mayumi)《I will give you 5000 yen of pocket money》
《Yay! 》 (Mayumi) 《Hahahaha》
《(Vibration sound of mobile phone)》
"yes"
📱(Kousaka)《Where are you now? Did you go to see Masaki Igawa? 》
《That's Ninomiya》 📱(Kousaka)《So he's already...》
《I understand》
📱(Kousaka)《What are you planning to do? 》
♬〜
《Ah... ah...》
《Wait! 》
♬〜
《Ugh...》
《(Rough breathing)》
《Ninomiya》 《Ah...》
《Ninomiya! 》
♬〜
《Shit...》
(Police Officer) ``It's okay to take your time.''
Please tell me about the situation when you fell》
``The person who was walking in front of me suddenly lost his balance.
Under the cliff
(Male)《I'm going to join the emergency services, so please clear the way》
``What happened? 》
《Right after Ninomiya saw me
I held my head and crouched down, trying to hide my face.
《Head? Did you talk to him? 》
《I ran away right after that.》
``He abandoned his family and was living a lie about who he was.''
She thought I had found out, so she ran away.
《We talk to Mayumi Igawa》
♬〜
(Mayumi)《Well then, Ma-kun, please come.》
(Tada)《I'm coming》
(Mayumi)《Be careful》
♬〜
(Tada)《Chase me! quickly! 》
《Ninomiya? 》
(Security guard)《Wait! 》
♬〜
"sorry"
《(Brake sound)》
"OK? 》
♬〜
《(Car lock sound)》
《I'm really sorry》 《No, don't worry about it》
《If you don't have ID, you can go to internet cafes etc.
I can't stay the night.》
《Oh, other than that, it's not that tidy.》
《Sorry》 《Ah, no...》
♬〜
"(knock)"
"yes"
《May I talk to you for a moment? 》
《Um…》
《My name is Tsujimoto from the Metropolitan Police Department》
《Eh... yeah...》
《I chased him away because he kept saying strange things》
《What is strange? 》
《He was in the same laboratory as me when I was in university.
He even called the company on my behalf to decline the offer.
``Didn't that happen? 》
《There was one, but not this person》
《What? 》
(Ichihara)《This is all about me and a friend named Okazaki》
``You were talking as if you were Okazaki.''
I don't know anyone at all》
``Did something happen? 》
《Where is Okazaki now? 》
《He passed away many years ago》
♬〜
《Which one are you? 》
《What? 》
《Did we meet somewhere? 》
《Ah... I'm sorry if I forgot》
♬〜
``What's happening? 》
《I think it said soft noodles》
(Kento)《Eh? 》
♬〜
"thank you"
《The teacher will also be full of cucumbers.》
``You'd be in trouble if you did that, sir.''
"good morning"
《Ah... Good morning》
《I moved to this area yesterday, so I took a walk around here》
《Ah... Is that so?》
(Kento)《Let's go》《Let's go》
♬〜
"Hello"
《Back from school? 》
Sorry, could I have just a glass of water? 》
《I got sick while taking a walk》
"thank you"
《Is that your father? 》
《Sorry to ask you something strange》
《Was it kind? father"
《I see.》
《My uncle’s acquaintance looks like him.《
If you'd like, here's another photo of my dad.
May I have a look? 》
"Yeah"
《Is this your father's? " "Yeah"
《It's taken care of, isn't it?》
"thank you"
♬〜
《Which photo do you like? 》 (Sage) 《Hmm...》
"long time no see"
《Wait》
《Tsujimoto》
《What is it? There is nothing to talk about》
《I want you to lend me a hand》
《You can't lend it to me.》
"I no longer have any relationship with my seniors."
``Why did you kill me? 》
《That's the only thing I didn't want to do》
《(Sigh)》
《I owe you one thing》
《What? 》
``You were deceived by a woman who was the suspect's lover.''
Investigation information...》《How many years ago are you talking about? 》
《That is already... the statute of limitations》
``Wow, you say that even in front of the big people, right? 》
《How far have you fallen?》
《I just want you to do some research without causing any inconvenience》
《I want you to match this DNA》
《Please, now I won't appear in front of you again》
《The only person I can rely on is you》
(Tsujimoto) 《My senior hated me.》
[The DNA of Masaki Igawa and Yusuke Ninomiya was matched]
《The DNA of these two people is...》
《Matched》
[Masaki Igawa and Yusuke Ninomiya are the same person]
《Is Mr. Igawa really your husband? 》
"yes"
《What happened to my husband...》
《I'll find out》
《So please do nothing and be as usual》
♬〜
Please wait
Please don't follow me, let me talk for a while.
I'm sorry, please
Now is not the time to worry about you.
Did something happen?
♬〜
《What! 》
Please tell me what...
Why do I have to tell you?
It doesn't matter, right?
there is
You are... my husband!
Huh?
What are you saying? what do you mean?
♬〜
Look, the three of us often went to Shonan Kaigan Park.
This is the park where we met the other day.
♬〜
Did you remember anything?
Ugh... no...
2 years ago you suddenly disappeared from us.
2 years ago?
What happened? I don't know
I've been with Mayumi for a long time, no! was with us
It's the wrong person
Apparently the DNA matched too.
you and my husband
When did you look into it? arbitrarily
Don't worry about it already!
♬〜
(Rie) Is that person okay? let me meet
Ninomiya might remember something.
But if I remember something unnecessary...
Should I delete it again?
♬〜
Ah...
Masaki Igawa is Yusuke Ninomiya
(Takagishi) After all, it didn't look like someone else's sky.
No, it's like a reporter's hunch when I see it.
It hit home haha!
But, well... why did you abandon your family?
Have you become a different person?
There are so many things I don't understand.
(Takagishi) Huh?
At first, Ninomiya abandoned his family and pretended to be someone else.
I thought I had chosen a new life
Is it wrong? I wasn't pretending.
That guy really thinks he's Masaki Igawa.
(Takagishi) What do you mean? Huh? Ah, multiple personalities...
Ah, no, but that's impossible.
Ninomiya-san's funeral was properly held.
It's full of strange things
When Igawa went missing due to an accident
A man named Tada from the same facility was frequenting Igawa's house.
What? Adultery? Haha, what happened after that?
When Igawa came back, it was as if nothing had happened.
Has it returned to normal? that
Hmm... well anyway
If Masaki Igawa regains Yusuke Ninomiya's memories
Does that mean you know what happened?
Or that Mayumi Igawa knows something?
♬〜
Excuse me, but could I talk a little bit about Masaki Igawa?
(birds chirping)
I was good friends with Masaki in college.
Was that so?
Um... please
Ah thank you sorry
Speaking of my husband...
When did you meet Masaki-san?
Why would you do that...
Although it was nine years ago
Huh?
My husband moved to this city to work at Harunagien, and...
Who are you married to? 5 years ago
(Mayumi) Um... what is that?
Do you have any other photos besides this?
Huh?
Why do you ask that? Of course there is
Where was your wedding held?
At Tokyo Lofty Hotel
Did Masaki make the reservation for the wedding venue?
What do you do when you hear something like that?
Did Masaki-san properly participate in the ceremony meeting?
Yes really?
What was the ceremony meeting like?
I don't remember even the details...
Please remember this is important.
Who did you invite? What's the weather like on that day?
Was it sunny? Was it cloudy?
Please come out!
I'll call the police.
Come out!
♬〜
(Osamu) What happened? Did something happen?
Yeah…
(Osamu) Is it something you can't talk about in your room?
Yusuke was alive
Huh?
♬〜
(Mayumi) Welcome back
yeah?
(cure) Impossible
For the past two years, Yusuke has been living as a different person in a different place.
So... have you met Yusuke-kun?
Yusuke-kun...
I lost my memory
Huh?
Yusuke's memories... all of them.
How can I get my memory back?
What triggers recovery in case of memory loss?
No one knows.
There are so many things that the human brain doesn't understand.
♬〜
Mayumi
yeah?
Let's get out of here
♬〜
Huh?
Let's live together somewhere else
♬〜
what happened?
i love you
me too
♬〜
(Takagishi) I understand the true identity of Mayumi Igawa.
📱(Takagishi) I just sent you the data, please take a look.
📱(Takagishi) There is a guy who specializes in reporting on court hearings.
Did you remember that trial?
📱(Takagishi) Yeah Nanami Ishino
📱7 years ago, I was sentenced to 10 years in prison for killing my husband.
♬〜
There was a prison sentence, right?
📱(Takagishi) Yeah, well, she killed her husband.
Why are you out there? 📱(Takagishi) It’s been about 10 years.
It's funny that it's already coming out.
♬〜
Mayumi?
Eh...
(cell phone vibration sound)
Did something happen?
Masaki Igawa and Mayumi Igawa are respectively
They were Yusuke Ninomiya and Nanami Ishino.
Huh? What do you mean?
My memory was altered and I was living as a different person.
📱(Kousaka) Wait a minute
Nanami Ishino, who can't do such a thing, was born 7 years ago.
She was sentenced to 10 years in prison for killing her husband.
Do you know anything about her?
📱This was the case that Kosaka-san's group was in charge of, right?
Nanami Ishino... That's certainly true.
I don't know what happens after I'm handed over to the detention center.
Why are people in prison exposed?
The same goes for Takatoshi Muroya.
I always thought he escaped from prison.
But maybe just like Nanami Ishino
Showing up as a different person...
📱What's going on?
I don't know…
📱(Kousaka) Don't go any deeper than this.
I have a feeling that something is wrong
♬〜
(sigh)
(sound of door opening)
(locking sound)
Mr. Igawa!
Please let me talk to you again.
There's no need for that
I'm Masaki Igawa
The one I love is Mayumi
Yusuke!
remember
Come back, Yusuke.
please
Me and Kento...
With Yusuke...
The three of us together again...
♬〜
why…
Ah...stop it!
Please don't follow me any further
I have to find Mayumi!
different
That woman is also not Mayumi Igawa.
Huh?
Can we talk for a moment?
♬〜
I've known you since college.
I want to know what happened to you
There's no way you'd understand.
I really want you to tell me this
What do you mean Mayumi is also a different person?
Her real name is Nanami Ishino
This is the murderer who killed my husband seven years ago.
Eh...
Why would such a person...
I don't know, but something similar happened before.
A person who is supposed to be in prison appears...
Mayumi is...
That's a lie, it's supposed to be...
I'm sure there's some kind of mistake
please remember
Why do you and Nanami Ishino live there?
Where did you meet?
I moved here nine years ago.
Mayumi lives nearby... No.
Until two years ago, Yusuke lived with me and Kento.
I have memories with Mayumi in my head.
remember
What happened two years ago?
♬〜
No way...
Does that mean Yusuke was also involved in a crime?
♬〜
(Tada) Oh shit...
Ah, Mr. Kondo, can I ask you to help me with the bathing?
(Staff) Okay, thank you.
(Rie) What's wrong?
Mayumi Igawa left town?
(Tada) Until I caught a taxi near my house.
I know, now I'm waiting to hear from the driver who picked me up.
Where did you go?
So you're saying you're listening to that right now!
Did you really get your memory back?
Well, I guess I ended up buying a lot at Costco.
Absolutely not (Tada) I'm just kidding!
You just told a joke.
It's okay, I've got my sights set.
Does that mean I'm a criminal?
The police have something to do with it, so I'll investigate.
Is that so?
Yusuke was also a police officer.
Huh?
I...
♬〜
(unlock sound)
(locking sound)
Someone came
(chime)
Mr. Sudo...
In the table light that those people gave me as a souvenir last year.
The camera was installed
Does that mean he was watching you?
Huh... why did you do that...
(Driver) Yes, I'm heading towards Shiokura Station.
Um... (Driver) Yes?
It's fine here (driver) Huh?
Please stop
(Ms.) Hey! Let's go! quickly!
Where are you going?
Maybe he was chasing Mayumi.
When I woke up in the morning, Mayumi was gone.
♬〜
(unlock sound)
Your memory has returned, right?
Where is that kid?
(Kousaka) Nanami Ishino seems to have regained her memory.
(Rie) Still thinking about her
What about your own wife? Is it love?
Mr. Kosaka is giving instructions, huh?
I thought we'd be together forever
I would do anything if I could go back to that time again.
Don't trust anyone